http://www.multipress.com/privacy-policy/

Benefits and Applications of a C-Frame Press
MULTIPRESS Adapts With Virtual F.A.T.!
What Does Your Process Require?
What is a 4-Post Hydraulic Press?
Pacific Press Announces Merge with Sister Company MULTIPRESS
Benefits and Applications of a C-Frame Press
MULTIPRESS Adapts With Virtual F.A.T.!
What Does Your Process Require?
What is a 4-Post Hydraulic Press?
Pacific Press Announces Merge with Sister Company MULTIPRESS
Welcome to our Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.
It is MULTIPRESS’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while using our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.multipress.com(hereinafter, "us", "we", or https://www.multipress.com). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the contact forms on the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, MULTIPRESS collects non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MULTIPRESS’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MULTIPRESS’ visitors use its website.
Gathering of Personally Identifying Information
Certain visitors to MULTIPRESS’ websites choose to interact with MULTIPRESS in ways that require MULTIPRESS to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that MULTIPRESS gathers depend on the nature of the interaction.
Contact Forms
Filling out a “Contact Us” or “Spare Parts” form will provide MULTIPRESS with your information. This voluntary submission of information includes: Name, Email, Company Name, Phone, State (when applicable), Country, Inquiry Type, Machine Specifications, and an optional message. This information is collected, stored, and used by only MULTIPRESS. Occasional industry related communication and information may be sent to the provided emails. If the content is no longer relevant to you, unsubscribing is always an option. Please contact us with any questions or if you wish to not receive these messages.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information. We will not share your information.
Links To External Sites
Our Website may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
MULTIPRESS Uses Google AdWords for remarketing
MULTIPRESS (https://www.multipress.com) uses the remarketing services to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt-out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, MULTIPRESS uses "Cookies," similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MULTIPRESS uses cookies to help MULTIPRESS identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.MULTIPRESS-torin.com, and their website access preferences. MULTIPRESS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using MULTIPRESS’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of MULTIPRESS’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to MULTIPRESS’ use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, MULTIPRESS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MULTIPRESS’ sole discretion. MULTIPRESS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
MULTIPRESS is located at:
MULTIPRESS
714 Walnut Street
Mount Carmel, IL 62863
United States
Phone: (618) 262-8666
MULTIPRESS Inc. | Phone: (618) 262-8666 | Fax: (614) 228-2358
714 N. Walnut Street – Mount Carmel, IL 62863
Copyright © 2020 QPI MULTIPRESS, Inc. All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site you agree to our privacy policy.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
It is MULTIPRESS’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while using our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.multipress.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or https://www.multipress.com). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the contact forms on the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
Read More
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
